(Penny:)Thanks.
(Penny:)Wow! What's with
the fancy spread?
(Sheldon:)My new roommate
is bending over backwards
(Sheldon:)to ingratiate himself to me.
(Sheldon:)Uh, nice touch,
by the way.
What do you mean "new roommate"?
What happened to Leonard?
(Sheldon:)The same thing that happened
to Homo erectus.
(Sheldon:)He was replaced
by a superior species.
(Raj:)I'm the new Homo in town.
(Raj:)That came out wrong.
(Penny:)All right, let me try this
again. Where's Leonard?
(Raj:)He's living at my place,
so I'm living here.
(Sheldon:)You're living here
provisionally.
(Sheldon:)But I must say
it's looking good.
Oh Leonard and Priya
are living together?
(Penny:)That's big.
(Sheldon:)No. Origami napkin swans...
(Sheldon:)that's the headline.
(Raj:)It's a good thing.
(Howard:)So do you know what kind
of research you'll be doing
(Howard:)at this pharmaceutical
company?